The morning jambo is now ours.
We are the stars of the chute area!
You know
Yay!
It started suddenly, didn't it?
Now.
I am going to give you a quiz about me, Yuna Nakamura, from now on,
I will ask you all to answer the questions.
The question is to see who among the members knows the most about me.
The person who can answer the question the most correctly will be given the title from now on.
Is it the opposite of qualifying?
That's what I'm doing.
For now.
Did I miss something?
Yes, yes.
But when I looked at the members, they looked familiar to me.
Naoo Yanagi.
Sure, sure, sure.
I've been watching him for a long time.
Scary.
I'm scared.
By the way, if you become the Naoo Yanagi this time, what will you do with all the gorgeous prizes?
No, you will be awarded the title of "Naoo Yanagi.
I see.
I'd like to get some sweets or something.
That's for sure.
Now that you mention it,
Well then,
Can we all hear it?
Can I hear that?
Thank you very much.
The person who gets the most correct answers will get the right to think about it.The person who gets the most correct answers will receive the right to be thought about.
The right to be thought about.
So maybe, depending on my rules,
By any rule.
I have gone berserk.
So let's begin.
Question one.
What is your favorite color?
My favorite color is...
Oh, I get it.
It's hard.
But I get it.
Not two colors, but one?
One color? Already?
But I've already told you this.
I'll keep this to myself.
What?
Don't tell me you're going to say it.
Oh, but...
What?
I know.
I can already tell what your favorite color is.
Oh, I know.
I can tell right away.
But definitely someone who knows me well can tell what my favorite color is.
Yes, I do.
Okay.
Please.
Okay, then,
Do you want to join me?You want to do it with me?
Together.
Ready.
Okay, then.
Yasumoto-san, pink.
Kokubo-san, pink.
Sakurai-san, purple.
Yes.
Then, please give the correct answer.
But I'm going to wear pink, light blue, and purple for my nativity costume.
My favorite colors are light blue and light pink.
Is that so?
I had them use those colors a lot.
I see.
Well, Aya couldn't come to my birthday party,
So, I understand,
When the designer saw the costume design, he said it was like this,
But I told him that it's my favorite color, and he said he's using it,
Oh, that, purple.
That must have been the purple. I don't get it.
You picked a totally different color.
Purple.
I have an image of it being used for a birthday party,
I don't think she'll like it.
I'm a little disappointed, though,
Aya and Yuuno got it right, since we're thinking about it together.
I wrote light blue for Yuuno.
Is that so?
That's good.
Okay, I'll give you 1 point, 1 point, 0 point.Okay, so one point, one point, zero point.
Then write 1 on the bottom for him.
Score at the bottom.
Oh no.
No way.
Masa's motive.
Oh no.
Let's go to the next question.
Okay, let's continue.
What is your favorite subject?
What's your favorite subject?
I don't know.
I feel like we've talked about this before.
Yes, we have.
Last time.
I know, I know, I know.
Did you ever talk about it when the three of us were together?
When Yuuno, Yuna and I talked.
I think we have talked about it.
I think we've talked.
Oh, I made a mistake.
Oh, I did.
With Aya,
When we were on the radio together,
I tried talking to her.
Oh, okay, okay.
Okay, bye,
Seino,
Social studies.
Math.
Okay, here's your answer.
What's your favorite subject?What are your best subjects?
Grain High and Science,
I don't know, I haven't done it recently.
What do you think was your highest score in math and science?
99 in science and 99 in math.
I couldn't reach 100 points.
What subjects are you good at?
What subjects were you good at?
Ino-chan and Ema are switching.
Ah...
I think we talked about how you and Ino are complete opposites.
So that's how you came up with it.
Ino's goal is to be really good at sukuri.
Yes, that's right.
By the way, the first time was the first time.
That's very sukkie.
I felt like I was going to be the first one to get it right the first time.
Maybe I'm mixing it up with Ino-chan.
You're mixing them up.
The words "Japanese" and "social studies" came to mind.
That's the goal of this project.
I'm mixing them up.
They are mixed up.
This time, I'm going to confront Japanese and Ema.
That means I'm in the leader's group.
That's great.
That's great. All the questions are being answered correctly.
Yay!
Ino-san gave me some feedback on my love for you.
Yes. Then, let's continue.
Next, if you could spend 1 million yen freely, what would you do with it?
If you could spend 1 million yen freely...If I had a million dollars at my disposal...
Nope!
What?
If you had a million yen to spend freely...
What type of person are you?
Wow! Nasty!
We never talked about that.
Never?
Not at all.
Not at all?
But you write such difficult and strange things.
I don't know. It's not a weird thing for Yuna. Weird thing.
That's rude.
This is easy.
What?
But it's something I like a lot. What you like?
It changes. Favorite person, favorite thing, favorite thing, something.
At any rate, I hit on quite a few things that I like.
I know, I know.
Okay, here we go. Okay, let's do this.
Otokatsu.
We buy a hot plate so we can eat monja at home.
Eat shabu-shabu so much.
Okay, let's see the correct answer.
If I were to spend 1 million yen, buy lots of cute treats for J.Y. Park that I buy at home,
I would make enough to keep in my yard at home and buy lots of yummy treats for him.
That's what I'm talking about.
Jake, either.
I, 6 screens of my cell phone screen will also be Jake. I love Jake, so I will use it for Jake.
But when I looked at the answers, I really should have chosen the answer about buying a hot plate so that we can eat monja in our house.
So, about 0.5 yen.
Dashi.Dashi.
Dashi. Severe. It's tough.
It's still tough.
But in a way, it's good to give it back to Jake.
It's different.
It's early. It's early.
So, who got it right this time?
Zero.
This question was indeed a bit difficult.
Let's move on to the next question.
If you had a time machine, what era would you live in?
Era?
I don't remember how I answered this question, but good luck.
But Yuna is smart enough to know the time period. I'm sure.
Unlike now, there should be many different eras.
Oita.
Is it really the era of society?
Elementary school student.
But isn't it like that?
Like which era you want to experience.
Society.
Society. Society.
It's luck.
I don't even remember what I said.
Let's all go. So, let's go.
Aya, the future.
Yuna, Meiji era.
Ema, Jomon Era.
Next, let's see the correct answers.
Heian period.Heian period.
Heian period?
I'm not sure yet, but I like it.
Was it appropriate?
Appropriate?
It was the Heian period, wasn't it?
I'm sure you just remembered it from earlier.
Yes, that's right.
He said it was historical because he doesn't like social studies.
The era that came to mind was Taisho, Meiji, elementary school, or Heian period.
I could tell a lot from the Taisho or Meiji Era.
I think I would wear the same clothes.
I was sure.
I saw it.
Heian period.
It's Heian period.
Your face is so white.
What?
Is that what you mean?
Your face is suddenly white.
Shall we move on to the next question?
Yes, go ahead.
Go on.
How would you compare yourself with the ingredients of a mongee gratin?
How would you compare yourself to the ingredients of a monger-aki?
That's easy!
Yes, it's very easy.
It's so easy!
That's what I'm talking about.
What's in a mongee gratin?
What?
You know, there's custom stuff you can put in.You know, there's something about putting in a custom one.
Oh, sure.
In a monje grill?
Gratcher.
I'm sure it's in there. What about you, Shimauchi?
I'm pretty sure it's in the family.
Definitely. - Okay, let's see.
Mentaiko?
Sorry, Mentaiko!
Mentaiko!
Mentaiko! Cabbage! Cabbage!
Well, here's the correct answer!
Let's say with these two...
Cabbage!
Yes!
I don't know why, but I like cabbage the best.
I see...
From here on out, the answers are getting better and better.
I'm getting more and more right!
I bet you put mentaiko in there too, right?
I wonder if it's like hakata...
Mentaiko?
When we eat monja at Yuu's house, we put mentaiko in it.
Oh, that's right.
By the way, what do you put in it when you eat it by yourself?
Thinly sliced rice cakes and berry starches.
And sometimes cheese.
Oh, you're serious.
So that's the theme?
Yes, it is.
So that's three points.That means 3 points
Three points.
Oh no!
That's 3 points.
Let's move on to the next question.
Next question
What is your height in centimeters? You can use a dictionary.
Dictionary?
Height.
What? Dictionary?
Well, I'd like to give you a compliment, but I didn't leak.
Oh, you didn't pee?
Yes, I did.
You didn't use a dictionary.
I didn't pee.
But maybe I'm still the same height, or maybe I've grown.
Heh.
I'll give you a hint... it's better than being in trouble.
More than a hint?
Oh, I know what you mean.
You'll know?
We don't even know how tall Rose is.
She's about 5'4".
Wow! I wonder how tall she is.
Okay, let's see.
154, 152, 152.
Oh! Oh!
What?
The correct answer is...
I found height 153 centimeters.
153 cm. I'm lost.
Maybe.Probably.
Well...
It didn't change much.
I didn't change much.
So I think I'm probably around 153.
Wow.
I don't know.
Maybe 153.
Oh, really?
Super bold.
I think my essential profile is still 152.
Oh!
Which is the correct answer?
The correct answer is 153 centimeters.
I was 152.
So zero minutes for all of them.
Ah!
You're right.
I don't know what height you're talking about.
He confesses how many centimeters he's got.
Let's go to the next question.
Next.
Nonakamaru, you're petting, Emachi, you're stroking, and Nakamura, you're...?
That's easy!
Very easy!
Oh, it's easy?
I don't know.
Super easy!
I didn't say it's that hard.
It's the kind of word that people would definitely think that already.
I'd be surprised if you didn't sing this one.I'd be surprised if you didn't sing this.
I don't get it.
I wonder what I've been listening to all this time.
Emo.
I don't know what you were talking about.
I don't get it.
I don't know.
Okay, let's do it.
Let's do it!
What's the character?
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Hi, there.
Yes, that's correct.
Hi, Mr. Heya.
Nonakamaru is petting.
Emachi is petting.
Nakamura-san?
Hi, Mr. Nakamura.
Wow!
That's all I can think of.
Hi.
Sure.
So that's how it is.
Aya is so confident.
Not at all.
What's that? Did you want it?
Sparkles.
Everyone is sparkling.
I don't study.
I can't handle it.
Hey, you're right about Mr. Hey.
Does that mean Mr. Heya is an alabam?Hi, you mean Alabang?
Yes, that's right.
No, you'll be working with your sisters.
Alabang...
We're not so strict here.
It's strict.
Strict.
You mean the first voice?
Because every time we go to a live show, there's always Ya-ya.
She's always been there.
It's always been you.
You mean, "Hi.
No one answered correctly.
If you look at it for the first time, you'll see...
I didn't get the "Hi" part right.
Next question.
Last one.
What's the luckiest thing you've done recently?
What's been a little lucky for you?
What's the luckiest thing you've done?
Three points.
It's the last question.
Three points, right?
Indeed.
Three points now.
Three points, right?
If I win this...
What's petticoat luck?
You don't remember?
I don't remember.
I don't know.
When people ask me about petit lucky events...When asked about petit lucky events
I didn't have anything petty lucky.
I had to squeeze out a lot of information.
That's why I don't remember it.
Telepathically.
It didn't happen.
Lucky thing.
I said it in the middle of all that.
That's what I mean.
So it really can't be helped.
Yeah.
Maybe it's not so inevitable.
Oh, no...
That's going to change.
Oh, well...
Laughs.
Okay, I get it.
Here we go.
Here you go.
Oh, no.
I made a delicious meal.
I got a lot of sleep.
Well then, here's the correct answer.
I wonder...
What's petty lucky?
Petty lucky thing
I didn't spend any more
I got about $1,000 out of the food.
I was so happy
With that money
I took a lot of fries
Wow!Wow.
You're quite properly lucky.
You're pretty lucky.
Hey, guys, I was just thinking about that.
I forgot about it.
I said it's not a big deal.
I had a bad feeling when I was waiting for you.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I really did find it.
I'm just making this up.
Okay, bye.
I found my wallet.
I found a wallet that I don't use anymore.
It was actually 800 yen.
What? Why this?
Seven hundred yen.
It was a little easier to see
Mr. Shaw, there's about 2,500 yen in there.
I wanted to say something like, "Yes, it's in there.
I did say that.
There were zero correct answers.
So...
Okay, then.
Shall we tally them up?
Yes, sir.
Mr. Sugata...
One point.
Mr. Sakurai
2 points
2 points2 points
Mr. Kojima's
3 points
So, Yunao is
Mr. Kuboyama.
Congratulations!
Thank you very much.
How are you feeling now?
I'm sorry, I shouldn't think about it.
I'm a loose cannon.
It's your right to think about it.
I'll let you think about it.
I'll think about it.
Thank you.
But from now on.
As Yunao of M-Che.
As Yunao.
You mean that you will live with Yunao on your back.
It's true.
That's amazing.
Why not?
As Yunao
I'm going to live with it.
That's great.
Is there any question you want me to guess for sure?
A question you definitely want me to guess?
Uh, but...
I'm sure Nakamura-san's question will definitely come up.
Nakamura-san's
Nakamura's question
Nakamura's questionQuestion by Nakamura
To the member who is going to answer
I have a few words for you.
Try not to make too many mistakes.
I would be very happy if you could do it.
I'd like to get a shock to see the finished video.
Please resume soon!
I'm so shocked!
How many of these were there?
Eight.
Less than half.
I think it's about half solid.
Do you think any of the other members would be able to answer that?
I'm sure they can.
I'm sure.
Ladies and gentlemen, let's not forget about monochrome aeons.
Yes, we have a favorite.
That's all for now, Genoa.
Bye-bye!
Please click the Good button and subscribe to my channel!
I'm waiting for your YouTuber comments too!
Bye bye!